ibiblio.org 2014-12-22

# Privacy Policy – ibiblio

ibiblio and The University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill are committed to protecting your privacy, and we will not disclose your personal information to third parties unless required to do so by law. By using this website, you agree to abide by this Privacy Policy as well as any other applicable [Information Technology Services policies](http://its.unc.edu/policies).

**Information collection and use:**

ibiblio may collect some information about how visitors access and use a website affiliated with the ibiblio.org domain and its contents. The information collected on this website is limited to non personally-identifiable information and may include information such as the computer address used to access the Web site. This data is used to improve website content and website management for users. Cookies may be used to facilitate the navigation of this site, but these cookies will not contain any personally-identifiable information. Other sites within the ibiblio.org domain may have different privacy practices. If applicable, consult the privacy statement on each page.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy:**

We reserve the right to update and amend our Privacy Policy as needed. A current version of the Privacy Policy will be posted on this Web site.

**Contacting us and reporting misconduct:**

For more information or to report any misconduct or abuse of this Web site, please contact us through the help request form.

15:45
  *[15:45]: 2010-12-03T15:45:12+0000
